Yes, yes, yes.
Please take a look when you come, it's really, really that disgusting voice. It's like this.
I'm really getting a voice from the pit of my stomach. I don't know you, Master.
Some people may be watching this, but it would be nice if there was a video, but it's just the truth.
It's just the real thing.
I just got a surprise... when I tapped my knee, I felt myself getting animated.
I'm going to make myself lively.
I'm so glad you're here and we're here today... and thank you so much... brothers... no... no... no... that's why...
I don't know why, but every year it's on Halloween, right?
I'm going to perform Mirei Hoshina's birthday solo live at ktz Yokohama on October 31st at 7:00 p.m.
I have a little event after the event of the birthday celebration, but the secret after the event is now!
I want to have something like this with Ra Nakamoto, and I want everyone to go to Nakamoto together.
I'm really looking forward to the end of the festival... and I'll be able to get a lot of fans to join me... and I'm sure it'll be fun.
I'd like to hold a birthday party for myself someday, where the people who attended the party come to the party.
That's great! Thank you all! I'm so happy for you!
Please come and see the birthday party.
It's been a year since then.
What are you doing this year? I've been so busy. Tuesday is the busiest day of the week.
I had a big week, and then I said, "No, I'm not busy." I'm in every class from first period to sixth period.
College student.
Last year, that's exactly what I was doing.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And, you know, I have interesting parents.
I waved my siren and my fenlight at them.
My dad sits down next to me, and he says, "Come on in.
What are you going to do with this? He said, "What are you going to do with it?
"Dad, are you sure you want me to wave it like this? I've got another one.
I've got another one... and I'm used to that room... so please number them consecutively...
So... that... thing... that Serhun thing... is it going, too?
What's that? A musical?
Yes, from October 6th to 10th, I'll be in the musical "The Girl Who Leapt Through Time".
I'll be in the musical "The Girl Who Leapt Through Time" from October 6 to 10.
I'll be performing at the Nihonbashi Theatre.
I'll be playing at the Nihonbashi Theatre.
I've been practicing for a while now, and I'm overworked, so please come and play with us.
I still remember the school stuff and the whole thing with my sister.
I want you to come out for a bit so I want you to come out for a bit. I want you to come out and see me.
I don't know, really.
I've had that happen, though.
I want to go see it so badly.
I'm so happy.
I'd love to see you too, Hirari-san.
I'll probably be busy that day, too.
It's from the 6th to the 10th.
All of them are busy.
And there are 10 shows!
The 6th to 10th of October is the busiest day of the year, in case you were wondering.
Such a pinpoint.
Master is fine.
My schedule is free.
I'm free, after all.
What do you mean?
No, no, no. By all means.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's fun, it's a really good piece of work.
It's a great piece of work.
So please come and see it.
So, that's all I have to say now.
I'd like to move on.
So, as I was saying, it's already Friday.
It's early, but Friday...
But Friday is Friday even if the month changes. Isn't it ranked first or second in the ranking?
But that's probably because you're a working person. It doesn't matter if they are students or not.
It's not for people like us who have irregular jobs. Fridays are very crowded and we have to do a lot of work.
It's probably the busiest day of the week.
Trains are also crowded, that's for sure.
It's true that you can't eat at the restaurants unless you grill the food.
I see. Those who work in the restaurant industry must be the busiest.
Yes, both at night.
Half. Half.
Well, let's see, there are a lot of people with such conditions, but let's say for us...
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday... what's your favorite day of the week? I've been asking that for quite a while.
What? Wednesday a little bit. Why is there a pause? Because it's in between.
It's also a holiday.
And I have to record "Devil's Advocate.
That's the best.
Yuichi Oda says it best!
It's fun.
Well, Wednesdays certainly don't give me a bad impression.
That's right.
Not so much.
You free? What do you want, by the way?
Oh, my God! I don't know... I mean, I have a day off on weekends, but it's not really related to our work,
But our work doesn't have much to do with it. That's right.
Mars and Thu are so great. The month is over,
Mars Tree. Tue imok fast talker.
I couldn't pick one, so I went with Kasei Moku.
Maybe that's where it's at.
And that's what Dreamland is all about, so going to Kāseimoku is a surefire success.
Oh no, that's right.
Maihama?
I knew it.
It's cheaper to fly to Maihama than to fly to Karsenmoku.
I see... so you talk fast there...
Yes, it's true.
I don't think people ask me what day of the week I like.
I think Fridays are the most popular, but I think everything is the same except Sundays.
I wonder if Sundays are special. Do you think people don't like Sundays? People don't like Sundays?
But there are also Saturdays and Wednesdays.
But there are people who come on Saturdays and Wednesdays, because we have the Devil's Advocate live on the air, and they're looking forward to it.
Is that what you're saying? The Kannai Devil, the heart and soul of the community!
Like a campaign poster? Like love and peace?
Love and peace, the support of your heart, Kannai Devil!
As I was saying, today is Friday.
But today is Friday, and it's Sweet Potato Day!
Why?
October 13th.
Well, this is something from the Edo period.
Back in the old days, when Japan was not so rich...
I mean, not so rich...
There wasn't always a lot of food.
Of course, if you have rice, it's fine.
But there were times when we couldn't get it because of the regulations.
At that time, sweet potatoes were very useful. Sweet potatoes are very strong.
They sell their stomachs, and they grow in places where it's hard to grow plants in this kind of land.
I see.
Sweet potatoes are originally from South America, Peru and other places that don't have sweet potatoes at all.
What?
It's not from Japan.
That's right.
It was introduced to China and other countries in various ways, and then came to Japan.
I didn't know that.
I think it was from Kagoshima or something.
That's true.
We have an image of them.
By the way, they are rich in starch.
Yes, it is.
Good source of energy.
High in vitamin c and fiber. Vitamin c is not easily destroyed even when heated.
It's the best, isn't it?
Recently, there are also those sweet potato brands such as Arezu and An no An sweet potato.
Nartokin, Beniharuka, Lachilan Benny...
Rachlan Benny... I've never heard of that!
Orojimakin, and other sweet and tasty varieties of sweet potatoes are also used in sweets these days!
I'm sure you'll enjoy the sweet potato one, but there are many kinds of sweet potatoes.
I've been talking to my stylist about the money I'm going to spend on rice, and I said it's the day for sweet potatoes, so I'd like it to be a sweet potato color, and the peel is...
If I had, I would have wanted the shirt to be yellow!
It would have been too much shirt. Fashionable!
I don't think sweet potatoes should be too drunk.
And now, some words of wisdom...
Let's see...
Words of wisdom.
This one's great, too.
Let's see...
There was a sumo wrestler...
There was a very strong yokozuna named Taiho.
He was a great yokozuna just before I was born.
He was a great yokozuna in the Showa period.
He was a great yokozuna.
And he had a really good-looking face.
Like this.
He's a very handsome guy.
I don't know if he's handsome or not.
Giant cannon omelet became a popular phrase.
Three things that kids like.
Everyone likes them?
That's right. Giants.
Baseball Giants, right?
And the cannon.
And the omelet.
That's about as high as you can go.
Isn't that great? Isn't that pretty amazing?
That's what he said.
Don't try to win. You can't lose.
I see. It's more frustrating this way.
No, no, no, no, I heard sumo wrestlers in the old days were great.
I don't know...
I only know what it's like...
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it... it was so real!
Come in!
Come in... I'll watch it.
Really?
The films we toured together were Sanctuary, Shinoko, Yamada and 999%.
Yes, yes, yes...
They're all from different genres.
We toured together in those three films on the spring tour.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I can't recommend them enough.
I can't recommend it enough. That was pretty dark, even for me.
I'm not sure I'd recommend it.
I don't know if there's a take on the whole thing, but it's interesting even if you want to see it.
Well, well, well, well... that's why Atsuto sent me this...
Atsuto said he loves sumo wrestling.
He asked me how much Saya-pon and Ebichu know about sumo.
Yokozuna, the highest rank in sumo.
Ozeki.
Wow!
Kannai, right?
Sekiuchi, yes.
Ozeki.
Under "ozeki"?
Kaku.
Kaku... Kaku of Kaku...
"Kaku" is a character for "horn".
What are you talking about?
I have no idea.
Hypole.
It's an angular distribution.
It's called Sekiwake.
Seki-hate?
Oh, that's where the Seki comes in?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ozeki seki division?
And in the three roles, I'm at the bottom.
Yes.
What is it?
It's a kind of cute role.
What? I wonder...
Ozeki Seki.
Yes, sir.
Seki?
I don't know what's going on here.
Dwarf.
Ah! Close!
What?
Close.
Little bird.
Ah! Close!
What?
It's like this.
Yes, it's like this.
But what's a little bird?
I'm a human being, just so you know, I'm doing it like this. But what's a little bird?
I'm a human, just in case. I'm doing this...
What do you do as a little bird?
Picks?
Pebbles?
Pinky?
No, no, no, it's not a pinky. It's an index finger.
Pebbles!
What?
Pinky knot!
Correct!
Kkknot, sekihyo, ozeki, yokozuna.
I really don't get it.
That's the three yaku.
Eh.
Strong is people
Yes, strong are people
And then there's a frontal below that.
Eh?
From the top, there's the first head.
The second, third, fourth, fifth, and so on.
Uh-huh.
And then below that, the next one...
Um, weight-wise, weight-wise...
Uh...
And then there's another one below that.
What?
Ten kilos, ten kilos? By the way, no, no, no, no, you say weight, so weight. And then there's that guy.
Like 10 kilos?
You say "weight"!
Weight is not a weight of weights, it's a weight of 10 kilos.
Money! Money!
This is quite surprising.
I really don't know.
I haven't seen much of it.
I've never seen it before.
It's kind of awkward, isn't it?
Well, well, well, well. Let's hear from you, then.
Let's see...
Oh, this again, this again, this again, this again, this again...
Mr. Yo!
Thank you, Mr. Nakahara from Kawasaki City
Thank you, Mr. Nakahara!
Thank you
So...
There was once a Daiichisha baseball cartoon
It's called Dokaben.
Dokaben.
The author was
The author is Mr. Shinji Mishima, and he was born in Niigata City, Niigata Prefecture.
And there, a road named "Dokaben Road" was built to commemorate the author's birthplace.
This is Yamada Taro. The main character. Simple and nice name.
Ganbare ganbare dokkaben Yamada Taro
No, I'm only talking about the king.
I don't know what "Dokka-ben" means.
At first I thought it was a work like that, like Papa Cooking Off Rice
Yes, yes, but that's where it came from
That's why he eats that big bento.
Oh, the "Dokkaben"?
Because he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot, he eats a lot.
No, but, um, can you please stop repeating yourself?
What is this?
Bento, bento, bento.
Bento, bento.
What is this, what is this, bento? Bento, bento.
This, you know, this manga called "Dokaben" has been running for a long time anyway.
Wow!
I wonder how many volumes it must have been, I don't know.
And after that, there was also a professional baseball version.
Oh, wow!
At first, it was about high school baseball.
And then you go to professional baseball.
Yes, I also go to professional baseball.
And the idea is a little bit crazy.
It's a little bit crazy.
There are a lot of guys that I don't understand.
In high school.
It's kind of weird.
Only one side of his head.
Like the guy with the brim of his hat and he's only looking at one side of it.
That's not the only case.
I mean, it's not scary at all.
The thing that made me laugh the most was...
Taro Yamada, the main character, goes to Koshien.
He goes to a school called Meikun High School and goes to Koshien.
And he's going up against a lot of really strong opponents.
But the one I thought was the most amazing opponent was...
Blue Train Academy, I think that's what they're called.
That's pretty cool.
We're going to play Blue Train Academy.
They have a night game in the fourth game.
There was a school that said they weren't good unless they played that way.
They use the lights to shoot.
They couldn't see the bullets because of the lights.
They'd say, "Where'd it go?
And then they win. I don't understand.
I don't know, it's like...
It's like a lot of cartoons have come in here.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was a little bit like science fiction.
That's what makes it interesting.
Wow!
I used to support them... back then.
Taro Yamada, Satonaka...
Iwaki...
I don't know anyone...
Well, well, well... it's not so bad.
This is a manga that Showa-era kids were probably obsessed with.
There's a cartoon "Dokagen Road" that Showa-era kids were probably obsessed with.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
What do you think of the live delivery?
What do you think?
But there's a lot of people playing Dokaben.
It's a big hit.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
So you started out in judo?
Hmm? Judo?
You did judo first?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Taro Yamada.
That's great.
Dokaben was great
Don't you know?
Anyway...
I don't know, I don't know... that thing like this...
Fly ball...
I guess this level of viewers knows a lot... about Showa-era stuff.
Dokaben was great.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, thank you very much! I'm with you!
I'm making that kind of face again!
Thank you!
I'm going to be a lot of fun!
Here we go!
Here you go!
Last but not least... we'll see you next week.
I'll see you next week.
After all, I'd like to know more about the effects of this week's show.
Okay.
See you next week.
Which one?
You're getting a little more original, aren't you?
Next week we'll be from 20:00 again. See you next week!